VICTOR AYOMIPO

WEB DEVELOPER. TECHNICAL WRITER

- □ vayospot@gmail.com
- **234-703-931-5618**
- https://github.com/Vayyo

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- ReactJS
- Sass, TailwindCSS
- NodeJS
- HTML & CSS
- WordPress
- Content Writing
- Marketing
- Al Proficiency

I'm a practical front-end developer, proud of everything I work on. I take pride in building interesting web apps, debugging, and simplifying complex ideas. Skilled in JavaScript and the likes of React, Tailwind, WordPress etc.

Even grandmas would be impressed by the results I produce. Let's build the ultimate user experience through your platform.

In my spare time, I tinker with algorithms and AI to build my own games. Because what's more fun than making a computer do what you want it to do?

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER (FRONTEND) Upwork

Aug 2021 - Present

- Fashioned a website so responsive, it could adapt to screens of all sizes, from a smartwatch to an IMAX screen,
- Developed web games using algorithms like DFS that are nearly undefeatable by users
- Learnt the art of debugging websites through a simple but effective means called "Dynamic Error Tracing"
- Collaborated closely with designers and backend experts, thus acquiring invaluable knowledge.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Jan 2021 - May 2021

Al's Pet

- Crafted an impressive website from scratch, giving a solid boost of 15% to the business's sales!
- Developed prototypes and mockups for 5 new features, making the UI design shine like never before!
- Sprinkled some magic on the website, thus reducing page load times by a whopping 40% using a clever media conversion trick!

CONTENT WRITER

Mar 2023 - Present

Semaphore / OpenReplay / and more...

- Authored engaging articles about AI tools that make developers' lives easier, that they could immediately put into action.
- Developed informative content focusing on developers, helping them reach wider audiences and boost their app's success.
- Worked magic with SEO tactics to optimize articles for increased visibility and search engine rankings.

EDUCATION

BIOCHEMISTRY
Olabisi Onabanjo University

Oct 2017 - Jan 2021

STRENGTH

- Eager to learn from the best.
- Time management, never waste a minute.
- Problem solver: cracks codes effortlessly.
- Reliable teammate, dependable through thick-and-thin.